<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AndroidDesignSupport</string>
    <string name="piano">The piano is a musical instrument played using a keyboard, which is a row of keys small levers that the performer presses down or strikes with the fingers and thumbs of both hands. Invented in about 1700 the exact date is uncertain, the piano is widely employed in classical, jazz, traditional and popular music for solo and ensemble performances, accompaniment, and for composing and rehearsal. Although the piano is not portable and is often expensive, its versatility, wide range, ability to play chords, ability to play louder or softer, the large number of musicians trained in playing it and its ubiquity in performance venues and rehearsal spaces have made it one of the Western worlds most familiar musical instruments.</string>
    <string name="saxophone">The saxophone also referred to as the sax is a family of woodwind instruments. Saxophones are usually made of brass and played with a singlereed mouthpiece similar to that of the clarinet. The saxophone family was invented by the Belgian instrument maker Adolphe Sax in 1840. Adolphe Sax wanted to create a group or series of instruments that would be the most powerful and vocal of the woodwinds, and the most adaptive of the brass instruments, that would fill the vacant middle ground between the two sections. He patented the saxophone on June 28, 1846, in two groups of seven instruments each. Each series consisted of instruments of various sizes in alternating transposition. The series pitched in B♭ and E♭, designed for military bands, have proved extremely popular and most saxophones encountered today are from this series. Instruments from the socalled "orchestral" series, pitched in C and F, never gained a foothold, and the B♭ and E♭ instruments have now replaced the C and F instruments when the saxophone is used in an orchestra.

The saxophone is used in classical music such as concert bands, chamber music, and solo repertoires, military bands, marching bands, and jazz such as big bands and jazz combos. Saxophone players are called saxophonists.</string>
</resources>
